cyprusjobs.com 2017-01-20

# Privacy Policy

**CyprusNet** is owned and operated by Dictiorasis Ltd a company incorporated in Cyprus trading as CyprusNet.com by Dictiorasis and/or Dictiorasis subsidiary, affiliate or related company (throughout our Terms of Use (see separate page) ' CyprusNet refers collectively to Dictiorasis Ltd and its subsidiaries, affiliates and related companies) (the ' Sites'). CyprusNet maintains the Sites as a service to its visitors, subject to the following terms and conditions concerning the use of the Site ('Terms of Use'). When you use the Site, you accept the Terms of Use; if you do not agree to the Terms of Use you may not use the Site. CyprusNet reserves the right to modify content on its Sites and these Terms of Use periodically without prior notice.

The following statement describes the overall Policies and practices of CyprusNet, including advertising on our network of websites, as well as across other internal sites, and products and services that are offered by the CyprusNet.

 **INFORMATION COLLECTED BY CYPRUSNET**

 **Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data**

CyprusNet delivers advertisements across multiple channels and media, including to web surfers who visit any of the hundreds of web sites that are a part of CyprusNet's network. With respect to individuals who visit those sites, we collect what is known as 'Click Stream Data.' Click Stream Data is anonymous, and includes information such as a web surfer's IP address, web pages which have been viewed by a web surfer, date and time by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us.

In addition to the Click Stream Data collected across, CyprusNet owns numerous web sites and services, and collects information at those sites.

As a part of the registration process at these sites, we may request and collect additional non-personally identifiable information about the visitor. Examples of the non-personally identifiable data that may be requested include age, gender, and interests. None of the foregoing information (collectively referred to as 'non-personally identifiable data'), by itself, or together, can by its nature be tracked to a specific individual.

 **Personally-Identifiable Consumer Data**

At some of the sites owned and operated by CyprusNet we ask people to register and provide personally-identifiable data. CyprusNet is committed to making sure that clear notice and choice is provided to all consumers before the personally-identifiable data is collected, and that they have opted-in to our use of their data. Examples of personally-identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, and e-mail address. Web surfers who have provided personally identifiable data may elect to have their data deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the Data Opt-Out procedures set forth below.

 **Other Information That Is Collected**

At some sites, including this one, CyprusNet collects information on individuals and companies who want to enter into business relationships with CyprusNet ('business information').

We maintain business information for purposes of administering the program, such as maintaining account information, sending payments, etc. We may share business information with third-parties who provide administrative services (and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information), as well as law enforcement or government officials as we deem necessary or appropriate.

 **HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED**

The non-personally identifiable data that CyprusNet collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content to individuals in an effort to create a personally relevant experience for each person. The data is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

If a consumer elects to provide CyprusNet with personally-identifiable data, we may utilize such data for marketing purposes. In addition, that data may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to that consumer's preferences and behaviors, and for other CyprusNet sales and marketing efforts.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Cyprus Publishers makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user 's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.cypruspublishers.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.cypruspublishers.com.
  * Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.cypruspublishers.com and other sites on the Internet. 
  * DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google through their AdSense program. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **SHARING WITH THIRD-PARTIES**

All personally-identifiable data provided by individuals is maintained in strict confidence by CyprusNet and will be treated with the same level of respect and care that CyprusNet treats its other proprietary information and trade secrets. There are instances, however, in which personally-identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third-parties, as described below.

The non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of CyprusNet on an anonymous basis. 

With respect to personally-identifiable information, CyprusNet may, from time to time, provide information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative services such as billing, delivery and pay-outs, or for other services related to providing a CyprusNet product or service. Any third-party vendor so used will be required to enter into a confidentiality and non-disclosure agreement with CyprusNet upon terms and conditions consistent with the policies set forth herein.

CyprusNet may also share personally-identifiable information with third-parties who enter into business relationships with us. These business partners may include financial service providers (including credit bureaus and insurance agents); non-financial companies (including retailers, online and offline advertisers, membership list vendors, direct marketers and publishers); companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, and others such as non-profit organizations. We may also disclose information to a third-party who provides substantially similar services as the original service signed up for, if we decide to stop providing such services ourselves. In such situations, we will provide our subscribers with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that CyprusNet is very careful about which companies it does business with.

In addition to the above, there is also the possibility that CyprusNet, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. If that's the case, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to your information.

Finally, CyprusNet may share information on individuals as it deems necessary to comply and cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

 **SECURITY PRECAUTIONS**

CyprusNet makes every effort to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We use state-of-the-art technology, including encryption, to ensure the highest security standards. Any data that is stored on CyprusNet's servers is treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. Nevertheless there are certain services that will give access of data to the public. These include, but are not limited to, Cyprus Jobs and Cyprus CV's. 

CyprusNet has a strict internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering CyprusNet's products and services. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, although we use industry standards to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating our security measures does exist.

 **Access to Data**

CyprusNet allows consumers who have voluntarily provided personally-identifiable data, access to their data to ensure that it is correct and to make any changes. Please contact us at [info@cyprusnet.com](mailto:info@cyprusnet.com). 

CyprusNet is committed to helping protect consumer privacy on the internet and actively monitors consumer privacy issues.

CyprusNet in its capacity as an advertising network may link and use information and material from websites found in the World Wide Web without the permission of the website owner. If however website owners do not wish to be advertised or listed in the Cyprus Network they should contact us and we shall immediately remove any links, logos, banners or other information and content relevant to their website.

 **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

The issue of privacy is an evolving CyprusNet is committed to the constant monitoring and examination of its privacy practices, and may, from time to time, institute changes to its privacy policy. In the event that any material changes are made to the company's privacy practices, we will promptly make changes to this privacy policy that discloses the changes through our websites.

 **Governing Law/Forum Selection**

All matters relating to your access to and use of the site shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Cyprus and the parties submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Cypriot Courts.

 **Contacting Us**

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding CyprusNet privacy practices, please send us an e-mail at [info@cyprusnet.com](mailto:info@cyprusnet.com).
